[{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664013142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7271,"timeElapsed":47482},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664016734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3590,"timeElapsed":51074},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664018934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":53274},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664033774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":14839,"timeElapsed":68114},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664044270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":10495,"timeElapsed":78609},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664048965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4695,"timeElapsed":83305},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664054109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5143,"timeElapsed":88449},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664058421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":92761},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664061957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":96297},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664068885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5863,"timeElapsed":103225},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664071429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":105769},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664075125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3695,"timeElapsed":109465},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664080717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5591,"timeElapsed":115057},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664084141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3423,"timeElapsed":118481},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664087165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3023,"timeElapsed":121505},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664090805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":125145},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664093813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3007,"timeElapsed":128153},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664095341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1527,"timeElapsed":129681},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664101285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4551,"timeElapsed":135625},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664104549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":138889},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664106261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1711,"timeElapsed":140601},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664109221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2959,"timeElapsed":143561},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664111837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2615,"timeElapsed":146177},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664115837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3999,"timeElapsed":150177},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3175,"timeElapsed":153353},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":156721},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664124341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1959,"timeElapsed":158681},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664128797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3711,"timeElapsed":163137},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664131805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3007,"timeElapsed":166145},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":167841},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664137101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3599,"timeElapsed":171441},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664141813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4711,"timeElapsed":176153},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664144029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":178369},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664146934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2904,"timeElapsed":181273},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664150797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3862,"timeElapsed":185137},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664153861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3063,"timeElapsed":188201},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664158717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":193057},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":196601},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664164109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":198449},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664166413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2303,"timeElapsed":200753},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664168597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2183,"timeElapsed":202937},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664171189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2591,"timeElapsed":205528},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":207665},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664175517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":209857},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664177133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1615,"timeElapsed":211473},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664180197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":214537},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":216233},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664183477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1583,"timeElapsed":217817},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3455,"timeElapsed":221273},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":223401},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664194069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5007,"timeElapsed":228409},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664198517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4447,"timeElapsed":232857},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664201628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":235968},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664203021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1391,"timeElapsed":237360},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2927,"timeElapsed":241232},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1223,"timeElapsed":242456},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2527,"timeElapsed":244984},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664217557,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6911,"timeElapsed":251896},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5871,"timeElapsed":257768},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664225188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1759,"timeElapsed":259528},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664227716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2527,"timeElapsed":262056},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664230900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3183,"timeElapsed":265240},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664233397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2496,"timeElapsed":267737},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2054,"timeElapsed":269792},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":8783,"timeElapsed":279320},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1344,"timeElapsed":280665},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5790,"timeElapsed":286456},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664257596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5479,"timeElapsed":291936},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1959,"timeElapsed":293896},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263412,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3855,"timeElapsed":297752},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664267644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4231,"timeElapsed":301984},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664270060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":304400},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":308312},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2335,"timeElapsed":310648},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664280356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3327,"timeElapsed":314696},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1399,"timeElapsed":316096},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1607,"timeElapsed":317704},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664287484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4119,"timeElapsed":321824},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":323672},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664290868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1535,"timeElapsed":325208},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1527,"timeElapsed":326736},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2319,"timeElapsed":329056},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664298020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3303,"timeElapsed":332360},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5735,"timeElapsed":338968},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":342336},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1743,"timeElapsed":344080},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1919,"timeElapsed":346000},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":348056},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3383,"timeElapsed":351440},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":353696},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664322524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":356864},{"subjectID":"vbrvutzt6g","prolificID":"67452be8638dfdb6708ae225","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421524edfb3fe6c713f70","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2319,"timeElapsed":359184}]